So far in our hotel dialogue we've finalized the number of guests dates room type any preferences and
到目前为止，在我们的酒店对话中，我们已经确定了客人数量、日期、房间类型、任何偏好和
answered any questions.
回答了任何问题。
OK now we need to get down to the personal information because that's what's needed in order to make
好的，现在我们需要深入了解个人信息，因为这是制作所需的
the booking actually put it into the system so that when you arrive here able to actually check in check
预订实际上将其放入系统中，以便当您到达这里时可以实际办理入住手续
in is what you do when you get to the hotel.
in 是您到达酒店后所做的事情。
The reason you usually don't do that at the very beginning is because they're probably not ready to
您通常一开始不这样做的原因是因为他们可能还没有准备好
write down that information.
写下这些信息。
So generally they will ask that toward the end.
所以一般他们会问到最后。
Different places are different but I used to actually do this job it was one of my first jobs and I
不同的地方是不同的，但我曾经做过这份工作，这是我的第一份工作，我
had to take reservations over the phone very often take bookings over the phone every day.
不得不通过电话进行预订 经常每天通过电话进行预订。
And this is how it went step by step.
这就是它一步一步进行的方式。
We had a step guide that we had to follow as receptionists.
作为接待员，我们有一个步骤指南必须遵循。
Anyway let me just get your personal information so I can finalize the booking.
无论如何，让我获取您的个人信息，以便我完成预订。
So I've got everything down but I need to connect it to something so that we can maybe call you if there
所以我已经把所有东西都搞定了，但我需要把它连接到某个东西上，这样我们就可以在那儿给你打电话
are any problems or charge you if you don't show up for example for the first night.
如果您没有出现，例如第一晚是否有任何问题或向您收费。
OK let me get let me get could also say just like we're ordering in a restaurant could I have could
好的让我得到让我得到也可以说就像我们在餐厅点菜一样我可以
I have.
我有。
That's fine too.
那也很好。
Let me get your personal information so I can finalize finalized means to make something final.
让我得到你的个人信息，这样我就可以敲定最终的最终手段。
It's a verb form any sort of process that has steps and then you want to make sure these steps are finished.
这是一个动词形式的任何有步骤的过程，然后你想确保这些步骤都完成了。
We could say we should finalize this before we go on to the next thing.
我们可以说我们应该在继续下一步之前完成这个。
Let's finalize it.
让我们最终确定它。
Very useful verb.
非常有用的动词。
OK let me just get your personal information so I can finalize the booking.
好的，让我获取您的个人信息，以便完成预订。
Could I have your full name and phone number now.
我现在可以要你的全名和电话号码吗？
Full name is generally first name middle name last name in English the last name is the family name
全名通常是名字中间名英文姓氏姓氏是姓氏
first name is the given name and the middle name is also given names who have family name and a given
名字是给定的名字，中间名也是有姓氏和给定名字的名字
name given name is the one that is given to you.
name given name 是给你的名字。
Family name is the one that you get because of your family.
姓氏是您因家人而获得的姓氏。
So my family name is pretty and my given name is Luke.
所以我的姓很漂亮，我的名字是卢克。
Ok.
好的。
Sure.
当然。
That means all right.
这意味着没事。
No problem.
没问题。
It's Luke pretty.
卢克很漂亮。
Now most people know how to spell Luke.
现在大多数人都知道如何拼写卢克。
Generally it's either spelled l UK E or L you see if I have a French accent maybe I have to spell it
一般来说，它要么拼写为 l UK E 要么 L 你看我是否有法国口音也许我必须拼写它
l you c and because that's how it's sometimes spelled in France but because I have an American accent
l you c 而且因为在法国有时是这样拼写的，但因为我有美国口音
they will write down probably l U.K. e because that's how it's spelled in America typically.
他们可能会写下 l U.K. e，因为在美国通常是这样拼写的。
OK.
好的。
So last name.
所以姓。
Last name my last name is weird.
姓 我的姓很奇怪。
I need to spell that because a lot of people think my last name is pretty.
我需要拼写，因为很多人认为我的姓很漂亮。
Actually it's PR I d d y.
实际上是 PR I d y。
But if you say it pretty pretty pretty it's pretty much the same pronunciation as pretty.
但如果你说它相当漂亮，它的发音与漂亮几乎相同。
Because when we say pretty actually we usually say that as a light D.
因为当我们实际上说漂亮时，我们通常说它是轻 D。
Pretty pretty pretty basically exactly the same.
相当漂亮 相当漂亮 基本一模一样。
OK.
好的。
So I need to be very careful and I need to spell out each letter.
所以我需要非常小心，我需要拼出每个字母。
And when you want to do that over the phone does it add it it added that it added a you will spell out
当您想通过电话执行此操作时，它会添加它吗？它添加了它，您将拼写出来
the letter say the letter and then another word that starts with the same letter just so it can't be
这封信说这封信，然后是另一个以同一个字母开头的单词，所以它不能
confused.
使困惑。
Can we do that with as in this is the phrase we use as in OK.
我们可以用 as 来做到这一点吗？这是我们在 OK 中使用的短语。
Sure.
当然。
It's loop pretty last name P as in Penguin pup of a penguin are as in Rhino.
它的循环漂亮的姓氏 P 就像企鹅的企鹅小狗和犀牛一样。
I as in India d as In dog D as in dog you only use the same one if it's two letters that are the same
I as in India d as In dog D as in dog 你只使用相同的一个，如果它是相同的两个字母
y as in yellow the phone number is 4 1 9 7 5 2 7 3 8 3.
y 如黄色所示，电话号码是 4 1 9 7 5 2 7 3 8 3。
And again I could write that with the parentheses around it like that.
再一次，我可以像这样用括号括起来。
OK let me repeat the number back to you.
好的，让我把号码重复给你。
We should we should do these gotta write the rolls again.
我们应该做这些必须重新写卷。
Receptionist guest receptionist guest all right.
接待员客人接待员客人好。
So the receptionist says Let me repeat the number back to you.
所以接待员说让我把号码重复给你。
Now there's going to be a mistake for 1 9 7 5 3 7 3 8 3 OK.
现在会出现 1 9 7 5 3 7 3 8 3 OK 的错误。
So it's actually 2.
所以实际上是2。
Right now if somebody gets a number wrong and you want to correct them don't say the whole number again.
现在，如果有人弄错了数字，而您想更正他们，请不要再说出整个数字。
If you say no no no it's 4 1 9 7 5 2 7 3 8 3.
如果你说不不不，那就是 4 1 9 7 5 2 7 3 8 3。
You say the whole thing again you're going to get into a situation where they're confused they're confused
你把整件事再说一遍 你会陷入他们感到困惑的情况 他们感到困惑
about which one was wrong.
关于哪一个是错的。
It's it's difficult because it's on the phone being on the phone with someone can be confusing.
这很困难，因为在电话中与某人通话可能会令人困惑。
For example hearing pretty and pretty pretty and pretty can be very difficult right.
例如，听到漂亮、漂亮、漂亮和漂亮可能非常困难。
So that's why we use this as in sort of structure to clarify it.
所以这就是为什么我们用它作为一种结构来澄清它。
And then when we have a mistake with numbers we use when we want to correct something only three numbers
然后，当我们对数字有误时，我们只想纠正三个数字
not the whole thing.
不是全部。
You can use the wrong number in the middle or the wrong number at the end or at the beginning but you
您可以在中间使用错误的数字或在末尾或开头使用错误的数字，但您
need to stress it stressed the wrong number.
需要强调它强调错误的数字。
And then the right number and the other two should be unstressed unstressed like this.
然后正确的数字和其他两个应该像这样非重读非重读。
No sorry not 7 5 3 it's 7 5 2 No sorry not 7 5 3 it's 7 5 2.
不，对不起，不是 7 5 3，是 7 5 2，对不起，不是 7 5 3，是 7 5 2。
That means all of the other numbers are correct.
这意味着所有其他数字都是正确的。
You don't need to change them.
您无需更改它们。
OK.
好的。
Got it.
知道了。
I see.
我懂了。
So that's how we do that on the phone.
这就是我们在电话上的做法。
This is a way to clarify when a mistake has been made.
这是一种在出现错误时进行澄清的方法。
And another very important thing is when you're dealing with Americans don't use for example double
另一个非常重要的事情是，当你与美国人打交道时，不要使用例如 double
double to double six triple three.
双到双六三三。
Don't do that.
不要那样做。
Don't do that you will confuse American English speakers a great deal avoid it just say the number one
不要那样做，你会让说美国英语的人很困惑，避免只说第一
by one one by one.
一个接一个。
OK so let's move on.
好的，让我们继续。
The receptionist says.
接待员说。
Got it means I understand the number.
明白了，说明我明白这个数字。
I've got all that information.
我已经掌握了所有这些信息。
Got your name and I need your credit card information or credit card number to hold the room hold the
知道你的名字，我需要你的信用卡信息或信用卡号码来保存房间
room.
房间。
That's the purpose of a booking.
这就是预订的目的。
It needs to be held usually hotels have the policy of charging you for the first night not all the nights
通常需要举行酒店的政策是收取第一晚的费用而不是所有的晚上
but the first night.
但第一个晚上。
If you don't show up if you make the booking and then you don't cancel 24 hours before then they're
如果您在预订时没有出现，然后您没有在 24 小时前取消，那么他们就是
going to charge you for the whole first night.
将向你收取整个第一晚的费用。
Sort of as a punishment or a fee.
有点像惩罚或费用。
Sure it's.
当然是。
And then you say the number.
然后你说数字。
And what's the expiration date.
还有保质期是多少。
It's done Ed..
完成了 ed..
And the code on the back it's OK.
而且后面的代码没问题。
So there's that code on the back.
所以后面有那个代码。
There's the expiration date when you want to say that very simply just use it or it is very very basic
当您想说非常简单地使用它或者它非常非常基本时，有到期日期
stuff.
东西。
But they will usually get those three details from you your name your phone number sometimes your email
但他们通常会从你那里得到这三个细节你的名字你的电话号码有时是你的电子邮件
address to send you maybe a confirmation confirmation and they will also get your credit card info in
发送给您的地址，也许是确认函确认，他们还将获取您的信用卡信息
case you don't show up and they need to charge you.
如果你没有出现，他们需要向你收费。
They need to reserve it for you so that they don't lose a bunch of money not being able to put other
他们需要为您保留它，这样他们就不会损失一大笔钱而无法投入其他
people in a room where nobody is going to stay.
人们在一个没人会留下来的房间里。